1. openBrowser("")
5. setViewPortSize(1920, 1080)
9. enableSmartWait()
13. navigateToUrl(URL)
17. custom.BrowserHelper.setupBrowserWindow()
21. waitForPageLoad(30)
25. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/header_digibox"), 30)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/icon-acount"), 30)
37. enhancedClick(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/icon-acount"))
41. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/field-account"), 30)
45. setText(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
49. setText(findTestObject("WEB/Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
53. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("WEB/Login/btn-sign in"), 30)
57. enhancedClick(findTestObject("WEB/Login/btn-sign in"))
61. waitForPageLoad(30)
65. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), 10)
69. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
73. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/sub-menu-iPhone 14 Pro Max"))
77. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), 10)
81. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
85. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/sub-menu-iPhone 13 Pro Max"))
89. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), 10)
93. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
97. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/sub-menu-iPhone 13 Pro"))
101. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), 10)
105. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
109. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/sub-menu-iPhone 13"))
113. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), 10)
117. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
121. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/sub-menu-iPhone 13 mini"))
125. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), 10)
129. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
133. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/sub-menu-iPhone 12"))
137. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), 10)
141. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/menu-iphone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
145. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Iphone/sub-menu-iPhone 11"))
149. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/menu-ipad"), 10)
153. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/menu-ipad"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
157. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/sub-menu-iPad pro"))
161. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/menu-ipad"), 10)
165. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/menu-ipad"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
169. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/sub-menu-iPad Air"))
173. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/menu-ipad"), 10)
177. mouseOver(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/menu-ipad"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
181. click(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Page Ipad/sub-menu-iPad mini"))